Miller, Howard F.; Papers apap088
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Public Service, 1941-1983, undated; 3; approximately 5.9 cubic ft.
  - Minutes of Legislative Budget Hearing on Budget Requests of Department of Labor, 1967 February 25 (Box 5 (3-Public Service), Folder 27)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee on the Transportation Program of Governor Rockefeller, 1967 March 22 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 1-2)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Administrative Board of Judicial Conference, 1968 February 20 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 3)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Transportation, 1968 February 20 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 4)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of New York State Identification and Intelligence System, 1968 February 21 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 5)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of New York State Police, 1968 February 21 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 6)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of New York State Office of General Services, 1968 February 21 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 7)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Health, 1968 February 22 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Social Welfare, 1968 February 23 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 9)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Housing and Renewal Community Development, 1968 February 23 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 10)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Public Employee Relations Board, 1968 February 26 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Civil Service, 1968 February 26 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 12)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Labor, 1968 February 26 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 13)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Commerce, 1968 February 27 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 14)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Education, 1968 February 27 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 15)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Conservation, 1968 February 28 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 16)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Mental Hygiene, 1968 February 28 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 17-18)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Department of Correction, 1968 February 29 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 19)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Narcotic Addiction Control Commission, 1968 February 29 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 20-21)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of Division of Parole, 1968 March 1 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 22)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of State University, 1968 March 1 (Box 6 (3-Public Service), Folder 23)
  - Minutes of Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee - Budget Requests of State University, 1968 March 1 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 1)
  - New York State Assembly Documents, 1968 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 2)
  - Assembly Candidate Correspondence and Position Papers, 1968 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 3)
  - Social Development Planning commission - Correspondence Regarding Day Care and Elderly Services, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 4)
  - Social Statistics and Programs Regarding Crime, Education and Employment, 1970; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 5-6)
  - Old Age Assistance Program - First and Second Drafts, Notes, 1970; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 7)
  - Social Development Planning commission - Title III, Older Americans Act, 1970; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 8)
  - Social Development Planning commission - Profile of the Elderly, 1970; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 9-10)
  - Social Development Planning commission - Child Development and Day Care, 1970; 1971; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 11)
  - Social Development Planning commission - Correspondence Re: Social Work Manpower Study, 1970-1971 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 12)
  - Appalachian Child Development Project - Memorandum, Status Report, 1971 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 13)
  - Teacher Retirement System - Pension Cost Reduction Proposal, 1976 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 14)
  - Director of New York State Division of Budget - Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1981; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 15)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Levittown v.s. Nyquist, 1980-1981 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 16)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Levittown v.s. Nyquist - Research & Responses, 1980-1982 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 17)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Correspondence & Position Papers, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 18)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Research Summaries, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 19)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Retreat Correspondence & Agenda, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 20)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Retreat Support Document, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 21)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Reports from Max Rubin, 1981; Undated (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 22)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Equity and Excellence in Education (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 7 (3-Public Service), Folder 23)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Equity and Excellence in Education (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 1)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Correspondence & Position Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 2)
  - New York State Task Force on Equity & Excellence in Education - Retreat Voting Document, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 5)
  - Budget Recommendations Related to Public Schools, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 6)
  - Budget Recommendations Related to Public Schools, 1981-1983 (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 7)
  - Budget Recommendations Related to Public Schools, 1983 (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 8)
  - New York State Assembly Local Assistance Fund Distribution by County - State Fiscal Years, 1958-1959, 1964-1965, 1965-1966 (Actual), 1966-1967 (Estimated) - Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 9)
  - New York State Assembly Local Assistance Fund Distribution by City - State Fiscal Years, 1958-1959, 1964-1965, 1965-1966 (Actual), 1966-1967 (Estimated) - Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 10)
  - New York State Assembly Local Assistance Fund Distribution by City - State Fiscal Years, 1960-1961, 1964-1965 (Actual), 1968-1969 (Estimated) - Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 11)
  - New York State Assembly Local Assistance Fund Distribution by County - State Fiscal Years, 1960-1961, 1964-1965 (Actual), 1968-1969 (Estimated) - Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 12)
  - New York State Assembly Local Assistance Fund Distribution by County - State Fiscal Years 1964-1965 (Actual), 1965-1966 (Estimated) - Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 13)
  - New York State Assembly and Senate Local Assistance Cities - 1964-1965 (Actual), 1965-1966 (Estimated) - Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 14)
  - New York State Assembly and Senate Per Capita Aid Distribution - Fiscal Year 1964-1965 (Actual) compared with Fiscal Year 1965-1966 (Estimated), Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 15)
  - Summary of Legislation 1965 Session, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 16)
  - New York State Assembly Analysis of 1965-1966 and 1966-1967 School Aid Increases and Tax Equivalents by School Districts and School Year, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 17)
  - New York State Assembly - Summary of Legislation 1966 session Packet 1, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 18)
  - New York State Assembly - Summary of Legislation 1966 session Packet 2-4, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 19)
  - New York State Assembly - Summary of Legislation 1966 session Packet 5-6, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 20)
  - New York State Assembly Detailed Summary of Legislation 1966 Session, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 21)
  - New York State Assembly State Aid by Function and Category State Fiscal Year 1966-1967 Compared with Prior Fiscal Years, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 22)
  - New York State Assembly Detailed Summary of Legislation 1967 Session, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 23)
  - New York State Assembly One Hundred Key Roll Calls 1967 and 1968 Sessions, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 24)
  - New York State Assembly Summary of Legislation 1968 Session, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 25-26)
  - New York State Assembly Comparative Analysis State Fiscal Year 1968-1969 with Prior Fiscal Years, Undated (Box 8 (3-Public Service), Folder 27)
  - New York State Assembly analysis of 1968-1969, Undated (Box 9 (3-Public Service), Folder 1)
  - New York State Division of Budget - Reports (Box 9 (3-Public Service), Folder 2)
  - Social Development Planning Commission - Medicaid Paper, Undated (Box 9 (3-Public Service), Folder 3)
  - Social Development Planning Commission - Services for Migrant Workers, Undated (Box 9 (3-Public Service), Folder 4)
  - Social Development Planning Commission - Reports and Project Information, Undated (Box 9 (3-Public Service), Folder 5)
  - New York State Assembly - Summary Analysis of State Aid to School Districts, Undated (Box 9 (3-Public Service), Folder 6)